(triumphant orchestral music)
(wind whooshing)
(metal clanging)
(gun firing)
(wind whooshing continues)
(haunting suspenseful music)
(cup clacking)
(people chattering indistinctly)
- [Secretary] Here
you go, Mr. Claybourne.
(employees clamoring)
I'm so sorry.
- No harm done as long
as the ink doesn't smear.
(employees laughing)
(employees clapping)
(people chattering indistinctly)
- Sir.
Um.
I just wanted to say
how grateful I am.
With all the layoffs, I didn't
expect to be here.
- You're young.
You deserve it.
- You are destroying
people's lives.
(security guard speaking
in foreign language)
- I thought he'd gone.
- And you can't even
face me, can you?
(security guard speaking
in foreign language)
- You got rid of all of us.
All the old guard.
- It's not like that.
- I helped build this
company from nothing.
It is my life!
What if I reduce my pay?
Please, I'm begging you.
- Why don't we talk about
this later, just us?
- There won't be a later.
(gun clicking)
(employees clamoring)
- Calm down.
Just calm down.
We can talk about it, I promise.
I promise.
- So?
- Just don't point that at me.
- Stay back, please.
- You're lying!
- Just don't point that at me.
- You're lying.
- Please.
Stop and just please think
about what you're doing.
These people,
they're your friends.
You're married.
You're married, right?
So am I.
Okay.
She means everything to me.
She's a kindergarten
teacher and she loves kids,
and we're desperate
for one ourselves.
But she just had a miscarriage,
which we're gonna
try again and...
Please, please don't, don't
take that away from her.
(gun clicking)
(gun firing)
(people screaming)
(Zach gasping)
(siren howling)
(people chattering indistinctly)
- [News Reporter] Good
afternoon, Los Angeles .
This is weather channel.
Today, sunshine will give way
to some rain...
- Oh.
- as we have some
cooler weather on the way.
(phone ringing)
Temperatures are
on the chilly side
between 50 to 60 degrees.
- Hey, babe, how are you?
- Yeah, good.
Just...
I wanna say I'm sorry that
I didn't call earlier
(siren howling)
and, you know, just
checking you're okay.
And you, the car's
still running good.
And you sure you still
don't want a new one?
And...
- Yeah, wait, wait, wait.
Slow down.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
(siren howling)
- Yeah.
Yeah, I know I should
have been in touch more
than I have been.
I just really need
to see you right now.
(birds chirping)
- I know, babe.
But I'll see you tomorrow.
You're still picking me up
from the airport, right?
- Yeah, of course.
Look, I've gotta go.
But I'll call you later, okay?
I love you.
- I love you.
(bird cawing)
(pensive music)
(people chattering indistinctly)
- [Julia] What?
How can you forget me?
I always wear the same clothes.
It's my lucky one.
But, look, I come here
all the time, okay?
- [Bartender] I'm sorry.
I've never seen you before.
- Give it to me.
Just one.
- [Bartender] You
have to buy a drink.
- [Julia] I said
I'll buy a drink.
Why can't you just
give me the olives?
- [Bartender] It's hotel policy.
- [Julia] Where?
Show me.
Where does it say olives cannot
be eaten without a drink?
- [Bartender] I'm sorry,
but if you continue
to be obstructive,
I'll have to ask you to leave.
- I'm not obstructive.
I'm not threatening you
or raising my voice.
No, just give me an olive.
- You have to buy a drink.
- I'll buy the lady drink.
Certainly, Mr. Claybourne.
(bowl clacking)
- [Waiter] Sir, can
I get anything else?
- Hi, I'm Julia.
- Zach.
- I know it seems odd, but I
could just kill for an olive.
- Not really my thing.
- No?
- Very good, sir.
The Desiree Dubois.
- It's Dubois. (laughs)
He'll go far.
- [Zach] Let's hope
he stays right here.
(Julia laughing)
(Zach laughing)
- [Julia] So, does
work bring you here?
- Yeah.
- [Julia] And that is?
- [Zach] Nothing exciting.
- Oh, I'm sure it is.
Tell me.
- Let's not talk about work.
Oh, my wife.
She's on her way over from LA.
I'm gonna spend a few
days in the Dolomites.
It's our belated honeymoon.
- That's very romantic.
- Yeah, I booked us a
whole deluxe package.
You know, comes with everything.
Spa, hot air balloon
ride, the works.
- Yeah.
And does she like olives?
- No. Why?
- They say opposites attract.
(Zach laughing)
Your trip sounds perfect.
- Yeah. Thank you.
We've had a
difficult time, so...
- Why?
Oh, I'm sorry.
- So, what about you?
- Oh, I'm still searching
for the right person.
- I meant
what brings you here?
- Oh, I'm just
waiting for a friend.
- [Zach] Hmm.
(Julia laughs)
- Wow.
Here's to you having a great
time with your wife tomorrow.
(glasses clinking)
- [Julia] Mm.
(phone buzzing)
Oh.
Do you know what?
It looks like my
friend's not showing.
(suspenseful music)
- Look, I don't where
you think this is going.
- (laughs) That's so
presumptuous of you.
- I love my wife.
She means the world to me.
- Thank you for sharing.
I'll remember that.
(engine rumbling)
(melancholic music)
- [Emmy] Why did he do it?
- I really thought
he was gonna kill me.
But all I could
think about is you.
And I told him that.
- Don't beat yourself up.
It's not your fault.
(engine rumbling)
- I'm really glad you're here.
- Me too.
I love my necklace.
Thank you so much.
(phone chiming)
(phone clicking)
- You'll be able to see
the Tre Cime on your left
in a moment.
And in 20 minutes
(phone chiming)
we get to Cortina.
(phone clicking)
(phone beeping)
- [Driver] I never get
bored of this view.
You know?
- Well, I can see why.
(phone chiming)
- You're missing all this, Zach.
- Huh?
Oh yeah. (laughs)
- What's that?
- Oh, no, nothing.
It's just, you know,
wrapping up with the deal.
Boring contract stuff.
- You gotta relax.
- Yeah.
Can't you leave work
for a few days?
- No, no.
Just let me clear this up
(phone clicking)
and then I'll be all yours.
(phone clacking)
- It's amazing.
(engine rumbling)
(birds chirping)
(cart creaking)
(door creaking)
- Here you go.
Took some persuasion getting
the chef to agree,
I can tell you.
(suspenseful music)
Sir?
- (gasps) Yeah.
(pen scratching)
(pen clacking)
- Wow. Thank you.
(door clacking)
(phone chiming)
(phone buzzing)
(sinister suspenseful music)
(phone clacking)
- Hey, baby.
- Jesus Christ.
- Jesus.
- (laughs) Sorry,
I'm switching it off.
- Good.
- You're so tense.
- You come first now.
- Thank you.
You gotta ease off.
I don't want you having a
heart attack or something.
Promise?
- I promise.
- What do you get me?
- Well, much to the disgust
of the Italian people,
we have pizza de pineapple.
- No.
- Yeah, I know.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
- My favorite.
- The chef wasn't happy.
- No?
Thank you.
How the hell did you swing that?
- Anything for you?
- Oh, my hero.
(lips smacking)
(Emmy and Zach laughing)
What did you get for yourself?
- Something that doesn't cause
great offense around here.
- I'm sorry.
I win.
- Barely
- Come.
(Emmy chuckling)
(lips smacking)
(soft music playing)
(glass clacking)
(soft music continues)
- Zach.
- What?
- I don't think
I'm ready just yet.
You gotta stop feeling guilty.
You mustn't blame
yourself, Emmy.
- I know.
(lips smacking)
- [Zach] We'll get there.
Just take as much
time as you need.
(soft music continues)
(fire roaring)
(lever clacking)
- Hi.
You ready to see the world as
you've never seen it before?
Yeah.
- Yeah.
- Zach?
- [Harry] Lovely to see you.
- Emmy.
- Nice to meet you.
- Welcome aboard.
I'm Harry.
- Hi, Harry.
- Good to see you.
Trained on the seas, but
destined for the skies. (laughs)
So, I'll be giving you
a quick safety briefing,
and then off we'll go.
No time to lose.
- Huh, you're American?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Born and raised in Chicago.
Moved out here about 11
years ago with my family.
Clean air, clean living.
(lever clacking)
(fire roaring)
Yeah, time to put the
pedal to the metal.
My grandson's fifth
birthday's coming up.
And I'm in the entertainment.
(Zach laughing)
I'm a qualified clown.
- [Emmy] No way
- From my days in the
circus when I was a kid.
It's a whole 'nother story,
but I'm waiting on a
couple of other folks,
but I guess it might be
us, so safety briefing.
Okay.
Ballooning is the safest
mode of air travel
as long as you follow
a couple of rules.
You'd be surprised to hear this,
but some people...
(engine rumbling)
Do not smoke or
vape in the basket.
Do not throw anything
outside of the basket,
and let me know if you
have any medical conditions
or if you're pregnant.
- [Emmy] No.
- [Harry] Okay.
Okay, then.
Don't touch any of the
levers or the ropes
or the instruments.
I can handle all this myself.
(ominous suspenseful music)
Oh.
- [Julia] Hey.
- Your timing is perfect.
- (laughs) Yeah, it looks
like my friend's not showing.
Thank you.
- [Harry] Welcome aboard.
- [Emmy] Hi, I am Emmy.
- Hi, I'm Julia.
- [Harry] Nice to meet you.
This is my husband, Zach.
- Oh, hi.
- [Harry] Harry.
- Nice to meet you.
- [Harry] Nice to meet you too.
- Well, (sighs)
sorry for being late.
So is this a special
occasion for you two?
- Mm.
- Yeah.
It's our belated honeymoon.
(Zach laughing)
- Oh, that's so sweet.
I can't think of a better
way to celebrate it
than up in a balloon.
- Yeah.
- Right?
You know what, I'm
not feeling so good.
I think we should...
Let's take a rain check on this.
- [Harry] No worries, Zach.
I'll look after you.
(Zach laughing)
- We've been looking
forward to this for weeks.
- Yeah.
- So I asked my assistant
to book us a private flight.
I kind of want it to be just us.
- I know, I know.
But it's just one
more, it's okay.
Have you done this before?
- Oh, yes.
It's like an obsession.
- [Emmy] Yeah?
- You can say that again.
- Right?
- And I can tell this is
gonna be a crazy good time.
- Right.
Well, then.
Mind you, will you just
take that corner, please?
Zach, you there.
Emmy, come on over here.
- Yeah.
- [Harry] And now our weight
is perfectly distributed.
Are you ready?
- Yeah.
- Let's go.
- [Emmy] Oh God.
- [Harry] Let it go, Zach.
Woohoo.
- [Emmy] All right.
(gentle melancholic music)
(Harry laughing)
- What the fuck
(Harry cheering)
do you think you're doing?
(flame roaring)
- You've got your phone.
Transfer the money now
and we can all enjoy our flight.
(Harry laughing)
- [Emmy] Amazing.
(birds chirping)
(flame roaring)
- [Harry] Never gets old.
- No?
- No.
Woo.
(flame roaring)
(lever clacking)
(Emmy laughing)
- Wow.
(gentle melancholic
music continues)
(lever clacking)
- [Harry] Let's get some light.
- Wow.
Yeah.
That's amazing.
- So cool.
(wind howling)
- [Harry] This is Bologna
Indian November Bravo.
We are in the sky.
- [Controller] Bolzano
Air Traffic Control,
flight acknowledged.
Just be aware of cloud
formation in the east,
it shouldn't affect you.
(radio beeping)
- Reporting all on schedule.
Everything is tickety-boo.
- [Controller] Thanks
for the update, out.
- So you don't
recognize me, do you?
- Nope.
Afraid not.
- [Julia] Okay.
- Oh, where do you think
you've met my husband?
- Oh, in Zurich. Just recently.
- Oh.
- I think she must
be mistaken. (laughs)
But I'm sure we can all
get to know each other now.
- That is an excellent idea.
Emmy.
There are some champagne glasses
right here
- Right.
Okay.
- If you'll do the honors.
I have a fast rule.
I drink champagne
in only two places.
One, when I'm in
a hot air balloon
and the other is when I'm not.
(Harry and Emmy laughing)
- Here you go?
- Yeah.
- [Julia] Woo-hoo.
- Oh.
(cork popping)
Oh.
- Hey.
(people laughing)
- This is voyage number 499.
(champagne babbling)
But I'm sure this flight's
(glasses clinking)
gonna be just as
special as the next one.
Here we are.
Enjoy.
- Cheers.
(glasses clinking)
(wind howling)
(birds chirping)
- So do you work in Zurich?
- [Julia] Yeah, I do indeed.
Yeah.
- Mm.
And what do you do?
- Oh, it's kind of boring.
I hassle people that owe money.
You know, credit control
for a private bank.
- Well, doesn't
sound boring to me.
- [Julia] (laughs)
That's very kind.
But let's not talk about work.
- Another.
- [Zach] I shouldn't.
- Oh, yeah.
I could never say no.
Can you?
- Huh?
(glasses clinking)
- That's Santa Magdalena
where we've just come from.
Really is amazing, isn't it?
- Oh, right.
- Thank you.
- There you go.
Oops.
Oh, it's surreal
- Up here, you really
get to reset who you are.
- Zach, look at these views.
- [Harry] You see that
ridge we're heading
toward over there,
that's called the Geisler Ridge.
And since there's no place
to land in the mountains,
we're gonna turn
around and come back.
- So you can steer
this thing, like, how?
- Well, you just
change altitudes,
wind direction changes
depending on the altitude.
- Well, that sounds
complicated. (laughs)
- Well, that's what
makes ballooning unique.
The journey is the destination.
You have to surrender
to the elements.
Flying this way is the quickest
way to escape your problems.
(wind howling)
Of course.
You can't stay up here forever.
- Have you always done
this job, Harry?
(lever creaking)
- Well, I was in the
Navy for a long time.
Finally retired.
Wanted to keep busy, so
I ended up in the air,
and I get paid for this.
(Julia laughing)
- Lucky you.
(Harry singing in German)
- High school choir.
You know, up here,
just got a rear
back and let it rip.
Sing to the world.
(Harry singing in German)
- Woo. Beautiful.
(glass clinking)
- [Harry] You have a go, Emmy.
- Okay.
(Emmy screaming)
(Emmy laughing)
(Harry laughing)
- I like that a lot.
Au naturel.
(Julia laughing)
(Julia screaming)
- Christ.
(Julia groaning)
- [Emmy] Okay.
- That's original.
(Julia gasping)
- (laughs) Right.
(eerie pensive music)
- Zach, go on.
- No. (laughs)
(eerie suspenseful music)
- [Emmy] I did it.
(eerie suspenseful
music continues)
- Whew.
I'm done.
- [Harry] Allow me
- Being so high up.
It does make you feel
kind of helpless, no?
- Yes. Yes.
Certainly gives you a
certain perspective,
feel you're distant
from everything else.
Makes you realize what
you really care about.
- For sure.
- Would you mind
taking a photo of us?
- Oh, I wouldn't.
Let's do it.
- And, oh no.
Come on, Zach.
Come on.
You gotta relax.
Come on, you look
so tense. (laughs)
And we don't want that, do we?
♪ Smile ♪
(phone clicking)
Beautiful.
- [Emmy] Thank you.
Harry.
- [Harry] Can I
take a photo of you?
Oops.
Oh, looking good.
(Harry laughing)
One of us?
- Mm.
Maybe one of us together.
(wind howling)
- [Zach] You enjoying this?
- [Harry] Very nice.
- More than the other night.
(phone clicking)
Hey, Zach, would you please
take a photo of me and Harry.
I would be ever so grateful.
(phone clicking)
- Oh.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
(eerie suspenseful
music continues)
(hot air balloon creaking)
(wind howling)
- [Emmy] Harry.
- [Zach] Hey.
- Up, up and away.
(flame roaring)
(wind howling)
(basket creaking)
- Ooh.
Geez.
Was worried there for a minute?
- Always in control.
- Are you?
- Well, yeah, if you
know what you're doing,
you can handle things
pretty quickly.
- Yeah.
And that can get you out of
awkward situations, I imagine.
- [Harry] Exactly.
- You need to take
care of this, and soon.
- Take care of what?
- I think if you show your hand,
you're gonna lose your hand.
- I'm really confused.
What are you talking about?
I'm not following.
- Friends, let's
try to relax a bit.
Things are getting
a little tense.
Why don't you just
enjoy this air?
Absolutely devoid of pollution.
- What, Zach?
(wings fluttering)
(eagle cawing)
- Whoa.
A golden eagle.
(laughs) That's incredible.
You hardly ever see them.
You're very lucky.
- Okay, turn the balloon 'round.
- It's understandable
to be a bit nervous
if you're not an
experienced flyer.
- No, no, no.
I said turn the balloon 'round.
- [Harry] It's not that simple.
- I don't care.
Make it happen.
- You obviously have
something to discuss,
but you may not do it here.
I will return you
safely in half an hour.
We are in the middle
of the mountains.
It's impossible to land.
(wind howling)
We need to ride
the currents back.
- Are you gonna play ball?
(Zach laughing)
- I'm not following.
- Yeah, 'cause she's
not making any sense.
- So you don't remember me.
- No.
- Really?
- No? Look at me.
You don't remember
buying me a drink?
- [Zach] I buy lots
of people drinks.
- (laughs) What?
Expensive champagne.
Desiree Dubois?
(Zach laughing)
Well, maybe all his
girls look the same
after a few glasses of bubbly.
- Yeah.
- Is that what it is?
(Julia laughing)
Look, your husband thinks
he can take advantage of me
and do whatever he wants
without any consequences.
Well, no.
- Really?
What are you actually saying?
- Oh my God, Emmy.
Don't even bother. (laughs)
- You don't know
anything, do you?
Well, that's so weird because
I know all about you, Emmy.
- Oh, you do?
- Yeah.
- Oh.
- I know things have
cooled off between you two
since you lost the baby.
- Oh, shit.
Look, I must have gone out
and had a few drinks, okay?
- [Emmy] So you did
have drinks with her?
- I wouldn't have said
anything that personal.
- No?
Probably just the things
have been a bit
difficult for her.
- That you don't want sex.
- Okay. Well that's bullshit.
- That's rich.
- Emmy. Okay.
- Why would you
even share that...
- Emmy.
- with the complete stranger?
- No, I wasn't a
complete stranger.
Tell her, was I?
He slept with me.
- Okay.
Well, that's a lie.
- Is it?
- She's lying.
- No, she's lying.
- Is it?
Is it a lie?
- Emmy, she's lying.
- Then how would I know
about this birthmark?
- Fuck. Don't fucking touch me.
- So it's true.
- Oh, Emmy, come on.
What? What?
Hang on.
You actually believe her.
Look at her.
- Please.
Will you all just calm down.
I can't believe this is the
way I'm spending the day.
- Okay, you can stay the fuck
outta this.
- Stop shouting at him.
- No, don't.
- Listen to me, please.
Okay, look.
Just look at me, Emmy.
Look at me.
I'm not lying, okay?
I swear.
- Why is she here?
- Because she knows who I am.
And she wants money.
All right. She's
trying to blackmail me.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- [Emmy] So why didn't
you just tell me that.
- [Zach] I wasn't gonna
take it seriously, Emmy?
She's fucking insane.
- When did all this happen?
- Oh, God, I don't...
A couple of nights ago.
I bought her a drink 'cause
the bartender gave her shit.
- So she made all this
effort to come on this trip
and blackmail you for that?
- I know.
Yeah.
- That makes no sense.
- Exactly.
- And we had one
drink, one drink.
- No, it was more than that.
- That's all.
Okay, maybe a couple of drinks.
- I don't know.
- I thought it was
a champagne bottle.
- Oh, for fuck...
I don't remember, okay.
I had a shitty day.
- Right.
Okay, so why didn't you
just tell me about this,
and how the fuck does she know
about your birthmark?
- Social media.
Okay.
There's a photo...
Everyone's got social media.
Photos of us in Hawaii.
She probably saw it there,
You can see that
in all of them.
- I don't do social media.
- You don't?
What are you
talking about?
- Of course you don't.
Okay.
Emmy, that's enough.
Okay, why are we even
arguing about it.
- Don't touch me.
- [Julia] You should have
just paid the money, Zach.
- Well, you think just
because I'm nice enough
to buy you a drink
that you can come
and blackmail me
with some bullshit accusation?
(sensor beeping)
- [Julia] Bullshit?
Really?
- I mean, if I had
anything to hide,
I would've just paid you, right?
But I didn't.
So I'm really sorry.
I think your little
game is over.
- Well, I don't think so.
What are you doing?
- Opening a vent,
we're getting too high.
- No, stop. Stop.
I said don't touch it.
(wind howling)
You, you're not
getting away with this.
- Mayday, mayday.
(radio crackling)
(knife clanging)
- Dammit, lady.
What the hell are you doing?
- [Julia] Well, we don't
need a radio, right?
If we escaped from our problems.
- [Harry] The only
problem we have right now
is getting this balloon lower.
All right?
I don't do that.
We're gonna run outta oxygen,
pass out and die.
- Okay. Listen.
You've made your point.
Please.
You're putting our
lives in danger.
Can you just let
Harry fly the balloon?
- No. Stop.
(dramatic music crescendos)
(Julia screaming)
(Zach and Harry groaning)
(wind roaring)
- [Emmy] Stop this.
- [Harry] I can't.
- Are you alright?
- Yeah.
(Julia coughing)
(Julia and Zach groaning)
(Julia groaning)
(metal clanging)
(gas whooshing)
(Julia groaning)
(Zach groaning)
(flame roaring)
(Julia screaming)
- [Emmy] Take your jacket off.
Wait, help her.
(Julia groaning)
(extinguisher whooshing)
(Emmy coughing)
(Julia groaning)
(wind howling)
(Emmy coughing)
- [Zach] Oh my God.
What has she done?
- We're still rising.
- I need the rope
to open the vent.
And now it's out of reach.
(Julia coughing)
- [Zach] What does that mean?
We can't get to it?
- Steady. Steady.
Okay?
- Yeah.
- You're gonna be okay.
(Julia groaning)
- Thank you.
(basket creaking)
- [Emmy] Harry.
What are you...
(wind howling)
(Harry whistling)
Harry?
- All right.
(Julia groaning)
(Harry groaning)
It's too...
(wind howling)
(Julia groaning)
(Harry gasping)
- [Emmy] You got it?
- [Harry] Okay.
Going.
(wind roaring)
- [Emmy] It's working.
(balloon roaring)
(Julia groaning)
(basket creaking)
- [Harry] Come on.
(Julia groaning)
- [Emmy] Be careful.
- No.
No.
(Harry screaming)
(wind howling)
(tense suspenseful music)
(birds chirping)
(body thudding)
(flesh squelching)
(wind howling)
- What the fuck?
- It was an accident.
- You fucking killed him.
- [Julia] It was an accident.
- Oh, my God.
- I didn't mean to.
- [Zach] Bullshit, bullshit.
We both watched you.
- No, no.
I didn't mean to.
- We both saw you do it.
We...
- I didn't mean it.
(wind howling)
(Julia gasping)
(sensor beeping)
- [Zach] Oh, my God.
(wind howling)
(frantic suspenseful music)
(Zach speaking indistinctly)
- [Zach] If we keep going
up, we are all gonna die.
- [Julia] (laughs) Good.
Good.
(Emmy gasping)
(wind howling)
- [Zach] She's collapsed, Emmy.
- [Emmy] Yeah.
- [Zach] What's happening?
- [Emmy] We have to
get to that rope.
(wind howling)
Wait.
- [Zach] Emmy,
what are you doing?
(Zach speaking indistinctly)
(zip buzzing)
- We gotta tie this on.
- [Zach] No.
Don't.
Please, it's not safe.
(Emmy groaning)
- [Emmy] Jesus Christ.
(suspenseful music)
(Emmy gasping)
(metal clanging)
(wind howling)
- [Zach] Hang on, Emmy.
I'm right behind you.
(body thudding)
(Emmy groaning)
(wind howling)
(metal clanging)
(basket creaking)
(Emmy groaning)
(suspenseful music)
(metal clanging)
(basket creaking)
(Emmy groaning)
(suspenseful music crescendos)
(wind howling)
(Emmy gasping)
(Emmy groaning)
(suspenseful music crescendos)
(wind howling)
(Emmy gasping)
- Got it, Zach.
Look, I got the rope.
We're going down.
Zach.
Zach!
- Wake up.
Zach.
Oh, God.
(Emmy gasping)
- [Zach] What the fuck.
- It looks pretty flat
where we're headed.
I think.,,
I think we might get
carried all the way
across the mountains
to the fields.
Maybe we just let it land.
Let me just close the vent
just before so we
don't fall as quick.
- [Zach] We should
tie her up, right?
And gag her.
- [Emmy] Why?
So she's can't talk
about what happened.
- No, 'cause she's dangerous.
(Zach groaning)
(rope buzzing)
(wind howling)
What else is in here?
(Julia screaming)
(Zach gasping)
(wind howling)
Hey.
Okay.
I really didn't sleep with her.
- [Emmy] What about
your birthmark?
How did she know
about your birthmark?
- I don't know, photos
on social media.
- [Emmy] She doesn't
use social media.
- Oh God. Seriously?
Emmy, look.
Okay.
We went out for drinks.
She came on to me,
but that was it.
Okay?
I really dunno how else
to prove it to you.
- [Emmy] Show me that
social media post.
You know, where you can see it?
I mean, you'd have to
be practically naked.
- I can't right now.
I don't have service.
- [Emmy] Well,
that's convenient.
- You know what?
I got 'em saved
on my phone, here.
There.
See?
(Zach gasping)
- Yeah.
I do wanna believe you, Zach.
- Look, I need you, Emmy.
Okay, I can't imagine
the world without you
and the family that
we're gonna have.
And when we get home,
I'm gonna get you the
best fertility doctor
that money can buy.
Huh?
- Yeah.
- All right.
Good.
Well, that doesn't look good.
(wind howling)
(ominous suspenseful music)
We're gonna crash.
Well, what would we do?
- Wait, this is closed.
We gotta change directions.
- Well, how are we gonna do
that when these don't work.
- We get lighter.
- We should throw her out.
- No.
Come on.
Let's throw these out.
(Zach groaning)
(canister whooshing)
Okay. I think that's working.
Yeah.
Okay, good.
- [Zach] Let's
take this one too.
(Zach groaning)
(Emmy groaning)
Right, next.
Come on.
Hey, watch out.
(wind howling)
(Zach groaning)
- [Emmy] Jesus.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Maybe we should leave one.
We might need it later.
- There's not gonna be a
later unless we clear that.
(wind howling)
(gasps) Oh, shit.
- [Emmy] what do we do?
- [Zach] Hold on tight.
We're gonna hit it.
(balloon rustling)
(Emmy groaning)
Oh shit.
Hold on.
(Julia groaning)
(Emmy gasping)
(balloon rustling)
(wind howling)
- Jesus.
(wind whooshing)
(Emmy gasping)
(balloon rustling)
(Julia groaning)
(wind howling)
(Emmy gasping)
(Julia groaning)
Come on.
- I don't know
(Julia coughing)
why you targeted me.
There were other
guys at the hotel.
- You think you
can come over here
and do what you like?
Is that what you think?
Huh?
- Stop it. Both of you.
(Julia coughing)
(wind howling)
- What the hell
(Julia groaning)
(wind howling)
(ominous suspenseful music)
Is this okay.
- [Emmy] I don't know.
(wind howling)
(ominous suspenseful music)
(wind whooshing)
(Julia sniffing)
- You have no idea.
Have you?
- I have money.
So do lots of guys.
(Julia sighs)
(knife clacking)
So, go on.
Why did you target me?
- You killed my
father, Hans Fischer.
He was my dad.
- That's the man
who took his life?
- He worked for
Krieger for 40 years.
It was his life.
But you just didn't
care. Did you?
- Of course I did.
It was a business
decision, all right?
One that meant the
company could survive
and hundreds of employees
could keep their jobs.
- But not that.
Just a worthless piece of shit
begging not to be flushed away.
- He had a great payout,
retirement ahead of him,
but he chose to end it all.
Not me.
- My father was
everything to me.
He was the only person
I could talk to.
And he was the only
person who cared for me
when I couldn't cope
with all of this.
But what do you understand?
You understand nothing,
you entitled piece of shit
with your designer suits
and your initialed socks.
You know I read up on you.
You inherited all the money.
You haven't even earned
it, you a piece of shit.
Huh?
- You're fucking crazy.
- I am not crazy.
- You are. You're fucking crazy.
- I am not crazy. (screams)
(knife squelching)
(Emmy speaking indistinctly)
- I'm not crazy.
- Julia stop, please.
- She stabbed me.
- I'm not crazy.
- I'm sorry what
happened to your father?
We both are.
We truly are. Nobody's
saying you're crazy.
We can help you.
We can say it was an accident.
- No, it wasn't.
- What happened.
Shut up, Zach.
Listen.
We can take care of all this.
We can take care
of all this.
- Yeah.
Please, please, listen.
Listen. Calm down.
- There is no
taking care of this.
Now my dad is gone.
I've got nothing left to lose.
- Julia. Julia.
- It's over.
Stop, please.
Please, please.
No, no, no.
Please. stop,
Stop, please.
Don't.
- [Julia] I can't
do this anymore.
- It's gonna be okay.
Please, let me help you.
Just give me the knife.
Julia, just give me the knife.
I promise you, everything
will be all right.
- I'm sorry for you, Emmy.
You never should have
married this piece of shit.
(Zach screaming)
(canister thudding)
(Zach groaning)
- What the fuck, Zach?
(Julia gasping)
- Zach, what the fuck?
- I was protecting you.
(Zach groaning)
(wind whooshing)
(Emmy whimpering)
- Emmy.
- Are you okay?
Let me see. Let me see.
(Zach groaning)
- Do something?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. All right.
Wait, hold it.
Hold it. Hold it.
Hold it. Here, hold it.
Oh, shit.
(Zach groaning)
- Oh god. (groans)
Emmy.
- It's okay.
- Could you hurry up?
- I've got this.
(Zach groaning)
- Coming.
Here, here.
Put this...
Hold this. Hold this.
Press down.
(Zach screaming)
(Emmy gasping)
- Oh God.
- Okay.
Sorry.
Just hold this up.
What else to do?
(eerie suspenseful music)
I think she was gonna
gimme the knife?
- [Zach] I had to put you first.
(wind howling)
(metal clanging)
- (exhales) I just
want all this to end.
(wind howling)
(cloth tearing)
(Emmy groaning)
(metal clanging)
It's getting bigger.
(Zach groaning)
We're being pushed
into those mountains.
- We need to do something.
- I know.
(wind howling)
Can we get these
burners working again?
(wind howling)
Oh, shit.
They're not connected.
- [Zach] Oh, God.
(Emmy groaning)
- Oh, shit.
(wind howling)
Yes.
Oh, shit.
- Emmy, we're losing
height real fast.
(tense suspenseful music)
- Why is it not working?
Oh, pilot light's out.
- What?
(switch clicking)
Have you got any other ideas?
- No. Do you?
- We should throw her out.
- What?
- She's dead.
- Really?
- What the fuck does it matter?
Also, she's freaking me out.
(lighter clicking)
- Here. Try that.
(Zach groaning)
- Fuck.
(wind whooshing)
- Wait.
You gotta turn this on
at the same time.
(lighter clicking)
(flame whooshing)
- Yeah, that's got it.
- Yeah.
(flame roaring)
(tense suspenseful music)
(wind howling)
- [Zach] Again?
(flame roaring)
- [Emmy] Yep.
(Emmy sighing)
Yeah.
- [Zach] It's working.
- [Emmy] Yeah.
(wind howling)
(tense suspenseful music)
- Oh no.
That ridge is too high.
We need to get even lighter.
Throw it all out.
(wind howling)
(Emmy and Zach groaning)
(object whooshing)
(Emmy gasping)
- We need to lose height.
There's another wind
current down there.
We need to catch it.
- What?
- We need to catch it.
There's another wind current.
(lever clacking)
(wind howling)
(Emmy groaning)
- Zach, we're getting too close.
(wind howling)
(Emmy gasping)
(tense suspenseful
music crescendos)
(wind howling)
(Emmy gasping)
Can you help me?
(Zach groaning)
- (groans) Fuck.
(wind howling)
- I can't believe she's dead.
- Well, it's not my fault.
Self-defense.
- I know it's not your fault.
I'm not saying it's your fault.
I'm...
Saying none of this
would've happened
if you hadn't bought
her her drink.
- What?
If I hadn't bought her a drink?
So this is my fault because
I bought someone a drink?
Are you trying to
blame this all on me?
- No.
- Do you have any idea
what it's been like
living with you the
last six months?
I've had to...
- Listen.
- practically forced you
just to come out with me.
- Yeah.
- You know why don't go out?
Are you fucking kidding?
- When I go for one drink,
and then all this happens.
- I've got a reason for that.
- It's not my fucking fault.
- Do think it's just normal that
you just go out for drinks
with a random woman.
- You have no idea.
Fuck you.
- Fuck you, Emmy.
- Fuck you, you fucking...
- Fuck you.
(Emmy screaming)
- Zach!
- Here.
- [Emmy] Zach.
(Zach groaning)
(Emmy groaning)
(Zach gasping)
(Emmy screaming)
(board snapping)
- [Zach] Emmy.
Emmy.
(Emmy groaning)
(Emmy screaming)
(Zach groaning)
(rope whooshing)
Emmy.
It's gonna break.
(Emmy screaming)
Take this.
- Zach.
(board creaking)
(Emmy screaming)
- Emmy.
(wind howling)
- [Emmy] Zach.
(Zach groaning)
(wind roaring)
(Emmy screaming)
(Zach groaning)
- (groans) Zach.
(Emmy gasping)
(Zach groaning)
(rope creaking)
(wind howling)
(Zach groaning)
(Emmy groaning)
(wood creaking)
(Zach groaning)
(Zach and Emmy groaning)
- Oh, fuck.
(Emmy and Zach groaning)
(Zach gasping)
You're okay.
- Where you...
Where you not gonna help me?
- What?
- When you hesitated like...
- Oh.
- Like you weren't gonna help me
- God no.
No, Emmy.
I was in shock.
I'm sorry I said
those things to you.
It was just frustration.
That's all.
I said you could trust me.
You can trust me.
Okay, I'll always
be there for you.
All right? Always.
(Emmy gasping)
Hey.
(tense suspenseful music)
(thunder roaring)
(wind howling)
- We're picking up speed.
(flame roaring)
Surely it can't make
that much difference.
- We're losing the hot air.
(wind howling)
(flame roaring)
- [Zach] Oh shit.
That hole's getting bigger.
- I think we have
to fix the balloon.
If we tied down that
piece of canvas up there.
Maybe we can stop losing height.
We could use this.
- You're fucking crazy.
- I don't see we have a choice.
(fabric tearing)
(wind howling)
(thunder crackling)
(rain pattering)
(wind howling)
(Emmy groaning)
- [Zach] Careful.
(tense suspenseful music)
(Emmy groaning)
- [Zach] Hold on,
let me help you.
(wind howling)
Oh shit.
(rain pattering)
(Emmy and Zach groaning)
(Zach groaning)
(metal clanging)
(tense suspenseful music)
(thunder crackling)
(wind howling)
(Emmy groaning)
(Emmy screaming)
(wind howling)
(Emmy groaning)
(rain pattering)
(thunder roaring)
I got it.
(wind howling)
(metal clanging)
(material tearing)
(Emmy groaning)
Catch it.
(Zach groaning)
(rain pattering)
I'm coming down.
(Emmy screaming)
(Zach groaning)
(wind howling)
(thunder crackling)
- [Zach] You have
to light the burner.
(Emmy groaning)
- Pass me the rope.
(Zach groaning)
- [Zach] You think it'll hold?
- [Emmy] It has to.
- Ready?
(flame roaring)
(Zach groaning)
(Emmy groaning)
I don't if this is working.
We're gonna hit that.
We're gonna hit it.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
(tense suspenseful
music crescendos)
(basket thudding)
(Emmy and Zach groaning)
(Emmy and Zach gasping)
(wind whooshing)
(hopeful triumphant music)
- It looks way
flatter down there.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I think we might
be through the worst of it.
- Made it.
We made it.
Oh my God.
We're over a field.
We're safe to land. (sighs)
(thunder roaring)
(hopeful triumphant
music continues)
(Emmy sighing)
(Zach sighing)
(wind howling)
(phone clacking)
- So much for escaping
from your problems.
(Zach groaning)
(Zach sighing)
- How did she know about
your initialed socks?
Zach, how did Julia know
about your initialed socks?
- I don't know.
I mean, they're socks.
It's not like I have to be
undressed to see my socks,
- But you got to
have your shoes off
to see the initials
on your ones.
Did you take your
shoes off in the bar?
Why would you take your
I don't know, maybe
if you've been walking
for miles in new shoes,
but yours are all worn
in and handmade in Italy.
Plus you told me you've been
stuck in the boardroom all day.
- Oh my God, Emmy.
What more do you want me to
do to make you believe me?
(ominous suspenseful music)
Whoa, whoa, what are you doing?
Emmy?
- Where's her phone?
- I don't know.
(wood creaking)
(wind howling)
(ominous suspenseful
music continues)
- Give me your phone.
- [Zach] Huh?
- If you got nothing to
hide, give me your phone.
- (sighs) Fine.
Jesus.
(phone clicking)
(ominous suspenseful
music continues)
- See, I told you
about those messages.
I'm not hiding anything.
Oh, come on.
This is getting ridiculous.
Just...
God, you smell good.
That's not me.
I'm gonna jump in the shower.
- [Julia] Don't be too long.
(ominous suspenseful
music continues)
- I really shouldn't do this.
- That's what makes
it so exciting.
(lips smacking)
You must be in a
really difficult place
after what had happened at work.
- Why?
You mean the guy
who killed himself?
He's just a worthless
piece of shit
begging not to be flushed away.
(lips smacking)
- It's amazing you
can be so strong.
- I thrive on it.
(lips smacking)
(Julia sighing)
- You happy now?
You found what you
were looking for.
(ominous suspenseful
music continues)
- You lied to me.
You looked me in the eye
and you just bare
face lied to me.
Repeatedly.
How many other women?
Do you even care?
- Of course, I care.
I care about a lot of things.
I care about having a family.
Not that that's something
that you can give me.
(Emmy sighing)
- So you're blaming me?
- I'm not the one
who's done nothing
but just wallow in their
own guilt and self pity.
- Guilt and self pity?
- Guilt.
You don't fucking know
what guilt is, Zach.
- Guilt is for the weak.
And that's hardly me, is it.
- Zach, you fucked a
woman you met in a bar
the night before we planned
to repair our marriage.
- Emmy, Emmy, Emmy.
Come on.
Listen.
What?
What would you have done?
Hmm?
- [Emmy] What would I have done?
- I mean, you haven't been
putting out for months.
- Putting out.
So all this just being
understanding and sympathetic
and giving me time
was just what?
Bullshit.
Just a fucking act.
- You can sound so
ungrateful sometimes.
Think about the
life that you have.
You've got this amazing house.
You got a shit-hot car.
- A shit-hot car?
This is insane.
- You want for nothing.
- Zach, can you hear yourself?
Do you think that's
the life I want?
Going to some pretentious
dinner parties with some insane,
humorless pricks who
care about nothing
but their position and how
much money they make per year.
- [Zach] Emmy.
- Who do you think you are?
- Emmy, stop.
- Stop?
- Before you say something
that you can't take back.
Do you know what
your problem is?
- My problem?
- You just don't
appreciate what you've got.
You know, where would
you be without me?
Really?
You're a kindergarten
teacher. (laughs)
And you would make more
money cleaning toilets.
- Fuck you.
Fuck you.
You horrible human being.
This is over.
I'm getting a fucking divorce.
And you know what?
I'm taking half of everything,
including your daddy's
precious company.
And believe me, it's gonna
be run very differently.
- Oh, sweetie.
Come on, you're
not going anywhere.
You can't afford to divorce me,
and you're certainly not
getting anything of mine.
Ah. Whoa.
(tense dramatic music)
(Zach groaning)
Fuck.
Emmy.
(Zach groaning)
(Zach screaming)
Emmy.
Emmy, help me.
Help me.
Please.
Please, do something.
Where are you going?
Emmy.
Emmy, where are you going? Emmy.
If you let me fall, they're
gonna pin this all on you.
They'll take you down.
You won't get away with this.
You're gonna spend the rest
of your miserable
life in prison.
Help me.
Emmy, come back, please.
Please.
Emmy!
What are you doing?
Emmy, don't.
Please don't.
(Zach groaning)
No.
Emmy, please.
Please don't.
Don't.
(Zach screaming)
Emmy!
(wind howling)
(Emmy gasping)
(Emmy groaning)
(wood creaking)
(ominous suspenseful music)
(Emmy gasping)
(wind howling)
(ominous suspenseful
music continues)
(wind whooshing)
(birds chirping)
(Emmy groaning)
(ominous suspenseful
music continues)
(Emmy groaning)
(ominous suspenseful
music continues)
(basket creaking)
(birds chirping)
(trees rustling)
(basket thudding)
(Emmy groaning)
(basket clacking)
(wind whooshing)
(Emmy groaning)
(Emmy exhaling)
(grass crunching)
(wind howling)
(lever clacking)
(flame roaring)
(somber pensive music)
(fire crackling)
(somber pensive music continues)
(frantic suspenseful music)
(frantic suspenseful
music continues)
(suspenseful ethereal music)
(suspenseful ethereal
music continues)
(somber pensive music)
(somber pensive music ends)